ILR School Metropolitan District Levi Strauss files /4266m
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Metropolitan District Levi Strauss files
1981-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4266m
1 folders
1 file folder.
Records (documents).
6198340
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 01, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Labor unions -- Clothing workers -- New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Levi Strauss and Company.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Metropolitan District Office.
6198340
- Levi Strauss Material, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: re: Levi Strauss., 1987; Text (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    ILR Memorandum
    Format: Text.
  - Item 2: re: Levi Strauss and Employee Ownership Conference., 1987; Text (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: ICB Briefing, 1995; Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 1)
    v.1:no.2 (1995:Winter)
    Format: Newsletter.
  - Item 4: Labor Relations Week, 1997; Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 1)
    v.11, p.86
  - Item 5: ACTWU-Levi Strauss Partnership Agreement, Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Collective Bargaining Agreement
    Format: Pamphlet.
  - Item 6: ACTWU-Levi Strauss Partnership Agreement, Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Collective Bargaining Agreement. Copy 2.
  - Item 7: Patterns, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    v.11:no.4 (1994:Sept./Oct.)
    Format: Publication.
  - Item 8: Peter Lazes to Doug Gamble, 1997; Letter (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Facsimile cover page and photocopied New York Times article.
    Format: Letter.
  - Item 9: King Jr., Ralph T. "Jeans Therapy", 1998; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photocopied Wall Street Journal article.
    Format: News clipping.
  - Item 10: Rifkin, Glenn. "Digital Blue Jeans Pour Data and Legs Into Customized Fit", 1994; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photocopied article
  - Item 11: Uchitelle, Louis. "A New Labor Design at Levi Strauss", 1994; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photocopied New York Times article.
  - Item 12: Levi-Strauss Update, Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no date
  - Item 13: "The New Cutting Room", 1981; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Report of the Technical Advisory Committee, American Apparel Manufacturers Association.